  "quiz_id": "20250723111109",
  "sets_data": {
    "set1": [
      {
        "_id": "月",
        "examples": [
          {
            "reading": "ゲツ",
            "type": "onyomi",
            "sentence": "月は夜空にあります。",
            "sentence_hiragana": "がつはよぞらにあります。",
            "sentence_romaji": "gatsuhayozoraniarimasu。",
            "translation": "The moon is in the night sky.",
            "explanation": "The 'ゲツ' (getsu) reading is used here for words related to the moon and its phases, reflecting its traditional association with the calendar."
          },
          {
            "reading": "ガツ",
            "type": "onyomi",
            "sentence": "月光が部屋を照らします。",
            "sentence_hiragana": "げっこうがへやをてらします。",
            "sentence_romaji": "gekkougaheyawoterashimasu。",
            "translation": "Moonlight illuminates the room.",
            "explanation": "The 'ガツ' (katsu) reading is utilized in this sentence for 'moonlight', a more direct, descriptive term."
          },
          {
            "reading": "つき",
            "type": "kunyomi",
            "sentence": "つきは夜に綺麗です。",
            "sentence_hiragana": "つきはよるにきれいです。",
            "sentence_romaji": "tsukihayorunikireidesu。",
            "translation": "The moon is beautiful at night.",
            "explanation": "The 'つき' (tsuki) reading is the most common and natural way to refer to the moon as a simple object."
          }
        ],
        "kanji": "月",
        "kunyomi": [
          "つき"
        ],
        "onyomi": [
          "ゲツ",
          "ガツ"
        ],
        "type": "example"
      },
      {
        "_id": "meaning_to_kanji_月_N5",
        "type": "question",
        "question": "Select the kanji with the following meaning - Moon, Month",
        "options": [
          "月",
          "録",
          "員",
          "原"
        ],
        "correct_option": "月",
        "correct_weight": 0.2,
        "wrong_weight": -0.1,
        "kanji": 1,
        "tags": "N5"
      },
      {
        "_id": "onyo_kunyo_to_kanji_月_N5",
        "type": "question",
        "question": "Select the correct Onyomi and Kunyomi pair for the following kanji - 月",
        "options": [
          "[\"ゲツ\", \"ガツ\"] | [\"つき\"]",
          "[\"ジ\"] | [\"や(める)\"]",
          "[\"タイ\"] | [\"からだ\"]",
          "[\"チュウ\"] | [\"なか\"]"
        ],
        "correct_option": "[\"ゲツ\", \"ガツ\"] | [\"つき\"]",
        "correct_weight": 0.5,
        "wrong_weight": -0.3,
        "kanji": 1,
        "tags": "N5"
      },
      {
        "_id": "kanji_to_onyo_kunyo_月_N5",
        "type": "question",
        "question": {
          "sentence_1": "Select the correct Kanji for the following Onyomi - ",
          "Onyomi": "[\"ゲツ\", \"ガツ\"]",
          "sentence_2": "and Kunyomi - ",
          "Kunyomi": "[\"つき\"]"
        },
        "options": [
          "弟",
          "過",
          "劇",
          "月"
        ],
        "correct_option": "月",
        "correct_weight": 0.2,
        "wrong_weight": -0.1,
        "kanji": 1,
        "tags": "N5"
      },
      {
        "_id": "日",
        "examples": [
          {
            "reading": "ニチ",
            "type": "onyomi",
            "sentence": "今日はいい天気です。",
            "sentence_hiragana": "こんにちはいいてんきです。",
            "sentence_romaji": "konnichihaiitenkidesu。",
            "translation": "Today is good weather.",
            "explanation": "The 'nichi' onyomi reading is commonly used for words related to time and days."
          },
          {
            "reading": "ひ",
            "type": "kunyomi",
            "sentence": "日差しが気持ちいい。",
            "sentence_hiragana": "ひざしがきもちいい。",
            "sentence_romaji": "hizashigakimochiii。",
            "translation": "The sunlight is pleasant.",
            "explanation": "The 'hi' kunyomi reading is used here to represent the direct experience of sunshine."
          },
          {
            "reading": "か",
            "type": "kunyomi",
            "sentence": "日が沈む。",
            "sentence_hiragana": "にちがしずむ。",
            "sentence_romaji": "nichigashizumu。",
            "translation": "The sun sets.",
            "explanation": "The 'ka' kunyomi reading is employed to depict the action of the sun going down."
          }
        ],
        "kanji": "日",
        "kunyomi": [
          "ひ",
          "か"
        ],
        "onyomi": [
          "ニチ"
        ],
        "type": "example"
      },
      {
        "_id": "meaning_to_kanji_日_N5",
        "type": "question",
        "question": "Select the kanji with the following meaning - Sun, Day",
        "options": [
          "係",
          "給",
          "央",
          "日"
        ],
        "correct_option": "日",
        "correct_weight": 0.2,
        "wrong_weight": -0.1,
        "kanji": 2,
        "tags": "N5"
      },
      {
        "_id": "onyo_kunyo_to_kanji_日_N5",
        "type": "question",
        "question": "Select the correct Onyomi and Kunyomi pair for the following kanji - 日",
        "options": [
          "[\"チ\"] | [\"はじ、は(ずかしい)\"]",
          "[\"テイ\"] | [\"ほど\"]",
          "[\"ザツ、ゾウ\"] | [\"まじ(る)\"]",
          "[\"ニチ\"] | [\"ひ\", \"か\"]"
        ],
        "correct_option": "[\"ニチ\"] | [\"ひ\", \"か\"]",
        "correct_weight": 0.5,
        "wrong_weight": -0.3,
        "kanji": 2,
        "tags": "N5"
      },
      {
        "_id": "kanji_to_onyo_kunyo_日_N5",
        "type": "question",
        "question": {
          "sentence_1": "Select the correct Kanji for the following Onyomi - ",
          "Onyomi": "[\"ニチ\"]",
          "sentence_2": "and Kunyomi - ",
          "Kunyomi": "[\"ひ\", \"か\"]"
        },
        "options": [
          "加",
          "陸",
          "好",
          "日"
        ],
        "correct_option": "日",
        "correct_weight": 0.2,
        "wrong_weight": -0.1,
        "kanji": 2,
        "tags": "N5"
      },
      {
        "_id": "浴びる",
        "examples": [
          {
            "sentence": "私は毎日お風呂に浴びる。",
            "furigana": "わたしはまいにちおふろにあびる。",
            "translation": "I take a bath every day."
          },
          {
            "sentence": "雨に浴びる傘は濡れる。",
            "furigana": "あめにあびるかさはぬれる。",
            "translation": "An umbrella gets wet when it gets rained on."
          },
          {
            "sentence": "子供たちは太陽に浴びる。",
            "furigana": "こどもたちはたいようにあびる。",
            "translation": "The children enjoy basking in the sun."
          }
        ],
        "furigana": "abiru",
        "word": "浴びる",
        "type": "example"
      },
      {
        "_id": "meaning_to_word_浴びる_N5",
        "type": "question",
        "question": "Select the word with the following meaning: to take a shower",
        "options": [
          "浴びる",
          "立派",
          "睡眠",
          "多少"
        ],
        "correct_option": "浴びる",
        "correct_weight": 0.5,
        "wrong_weight": -0.3,
        "kanji_only": "浴",
        "kanji_type": "浴:N2",
        "furigana": "abiru",
        "vocab": 1,
        "tags": "N5"
      },
      {
        "_id": "word_to_meaning_浴びる_N5",
        "type": "question",
        "question": "Select the meaning for the word: 浴びる",
        "options": [
          "to take a shower",
          "pencil",
          "verbal message",
          "precipitous; rugged; inaccessible; impregnable; steep​; grim; severe; stern​"
        ],
        "correct_option": "to take a shower",
        "correct_weight": 0.5,
        "wrong_weight": -0.3,
        "kanji_only": "浴",
        "kanji_type": "浴:N2",
        "furigana": "abiru",
        "vocab": 1,
        "tags": "N5"
      },
      {
        "_id": "危ない",
        "examples": [
          {
            "sentence": "この道は危ないから気を付けてください。",
            "furigana": "このみちはあぶないからきをつけてください。",
            "translation": "This road is dangerous, so please be careful."
          },
          {
            "sentence": "子供は危ない場所に一人で行かないで。",
            "furigana": "こどもはあぶないばしょにひとりでいかないで。",
            "translation": "Children should not go alone to dangerous places."
          },
          {
            "sentence": "転ぶかもしれない、危ないです。",
            "furigana": "ころぶかもしれない、あぶないです。",
            "translation": "There is a risk of falling, it's dangerous."
          }
        ],
        "furigana": "abunai",
        "word": "危ない",
        "type": "example"
      },
      {
        "_id": "meaning_to_word_危ない_N5",
        "type": "question",
        "question": "Select the word with the following meaning: dangerous, risky",
        "options": [
          "厚い",
          "危ない",
          "追加",
          "保証"
        ],
        "correct_option": "危ない",
        "correct_weight": 0.5,
        "wrong_weight": -0.3,
        "kanji_only": "危",
        "kanji_type": "危:N3",
        "furigana": "abunai",
        "vocab": 2,
        "tags": "N5"
      },
      {
        "_id": "word_to_meaning_危ない_N5",
        "type": "question",
        "question": "Select the meaning for the word: 危ない",
        "options": [
          "aviation, flight",
          "unbalanced diet​",
          "departure of a vehicle",
          "dangerous, risky"
        ],
        "correct_option": "dangerous, risky",
        "correct_weight": 0.5,
        "wrong_weight": -0.3,
        "kanji_only": "危",
        "kanji_type": "危:N3",
        "furigana": "abunai",
        "vocab": 2,
        "tags": "N5"
      }
    ],
    "set2": [
      {
        "_id": "七",
        "examples": [
          {
            "reading": "シチ",
            "type": "onyomi",
            "sentence": "七日 (ななじつ) は、日本の伝統的な日です。",
            "sentence_hiragana": "なのか (ななじつ) は、にっぽんのでんとうてきなにちです。",
            "sentence_romaji": "nanoka (nanajitsu) ha、nipponnodentoutekinanichidesu。",
            "translation": "The seventh day is a traditional day in Japan.",
            "explanation": "The onyomi 'シチ' is used here because '七日' (nana-jitsu) is a common compound word representing the seventh day of the week and important historical dates."
          },
          {
            "reading": "なな・つ",
            "type": "kunyomi",
            "sentence": "七人のナナは、魔法の力を持っています。",
            "sentence_hiragana": "しちにんのななは、まほうのちからをもっています。",
            "sentence_romaji": "shichininnonanaha、mahounochikarawomotsuteimasu。",
            "translation": "Seven Seven's possess magical power.",
            "explanation": "The kunyomi 'なな' is used to represent the number seven in a more descriptive or narrative context, as it's commonly used to refer to individuals."
          }
        ],
        "kanji": "七",
        "kunyomi": [
          "なな・つ"
        ],
        "onyomi": [
          "シチ"
        ],
        "type": "example"
      },
      {
        "_id": "meaning_to_kanji_七_N5",
        "type": "question",
        "question": "Select the kanji with the following meaning - Seven",
        "options": [
          "備",
          "律",
          "粉",
          "七"
        ],
        "correct_option": "七",
        "correct_weight": 0.2,
        "wrong_weight": -0.1,
        "kanji": 3,
        "tags": "N5"
      },
      {
        "_id": "onyo_kunyo_to_kanji_七_N5",
        "type": "question",
        "question": "Select the correct Onyomi and Kunyomi pair for the following kanji - 七",
        "options": [
          "[\"シチ\"] | [\"なな・つ\"]",
          "[\"キョウ\"] | [\"とも\"]",
          "[\"フク\"] | []",
          "[\"ユウ\"] | [\"いさ(む)\"]"
        ],
        "correct_option": "[\"シチ\"] | [\"なな・つ\"]",
        "correct_weight": 0.5,
        "wrong_weight": -0.3,
        "kanji": 3,
        "tags": "N5"
      },
      {
        "_id": "kanji_to_onyo_kunyo_七_N5",
        "type": "question",
        "question": {
          "sentence_1": "Select the correct Kanji for the following Onyomi - ",
          "Onyomi": "[\"シチ\"]",
          "sentence_2": "and Kunyomi - ",
          "Kunyomi": "[\"なな・つ\"]"
        },
        "options": [
          "時",
          "姓",
          "求",
          "七"
        ],
        "correct_option": "七",
        "correct_weight": 0.2,
        "wrong_weight": -0.1,
        "kanji": 3,
        "tags": "N5"
      },
      {
        "_id": "大",
        "examples": [
          {
            "reading": "ダイ",
            "type": "onyomi",
            "sentence": "大きな山だ。",
            "sentence_hiragana": "おおきなやまだ。",
            "sentence_romaji": "ookinayamada。",
            "translation": "It is a large mountain.",
            "explanation": "The onyomi 'dai' is used for large, expansive things like mountains or areas."
          },
          {
            "reading": "おお・きい",
            "type": "kunyomi",
            "sentence": "この絵は大きい。",
            "sentence_hiragana": "このえはおおきい。",
            "sentence_romaji": "konoehaookii。",
            "translation": "This picture is big.",
            "explanation": "The kunyomi 'ooi' is used for a direct description of size, particularly when comparing objects."
          }
        ],
        "kanji": "大",
        "kunyomi": [
          "おお・きい"
        ],
        "onyomi": [
          "ダイ"
        ],
        "type": "example"
      },
      {
        "_id": "meaning_to_kanji_大_N5",
        "type": "question",
        "question": "Select the kanji with the following meaning - Big, Large",
        "options": [
          "大",
          "伺",
          "担",
          "過"
        ],
        "correct_option": "大",
        "correct_weight": 0.2,
        "wrong_weight": -0.1,
        "kanji": 4,
        "tags": "N5"
      },
      {
        "_id": "onyo_kunyo_to_kanji_大_N5",
        "type": "question",
        "question": "Select the correct Onyomi and Kunyomi pair for the following kanji - 大",
        "options": [
          "[] | [\"だ・す\", \"で・る\"]",
          "[\"ダイ\"] | [\"おお・きい\"]",
          "[] | [\"しろ\", \"しろ・い\"]",
          "[\"ヘン\"] | [\"あた(り)、 ほと(り)\"]"
        ],
        "correct_option": "[\"ダイ\"] | [\"おお・きい\"]",
        "correct_weight": 0.5,
        "wrong_weight": -0.3,
        "kanji": 4,
        "tags": "N5"
      },
      {
        "_id": "kanji_to_onyo_kunyo_大_N5",
        "type": "question",
        "question": {
          "sentence_1": "Select the correct Kanji for the following Onyomi - ",
          "Onyomi": "[\"ダイ\"]",
          "sentence_2": "and Kunyomi - ",
          "Kunyomi": "[\"おお・きい\"]"
        },
        "options": [
          "紙",
          "面",
          "担",
          "大"
        ],
        "correct_option": "大",
        "correct_weight": 0.2,
        "wrong_weight": -0.1,
        "kanji": 4,
        "tags": "N5"
      },
      {
        "_id": "あげる",
        "examples": [
          {
            "sentence": "プレゼントをあげる。",
            "furigana": "プレゼントをあげる。",
            "translation": "I will give you a present."
          },
          {
            "sentence": "りんごをあげる。",
            "furigana": "りんごをあげる。",
            "translation": "I'm giving you an apple."
          },
          {
            "sentence": "宿題をあげる。",
            "furigana": "しゅくだいをあげる。",
            "translation": "I'll do your homework."
          }
        ],
        "furigana": "ageru",
        "word": "あげる",
        "type": "example"
      },
      {
        "_id": "meaning_to_word_あげる_N5",
        "type": "question",
        "question": "Select the word with the following meaning: to give",
        "options": [
          "洗い出す",
          "到底",
          "早朝",
          "あげる"
        ],
        "correct_option": "あげる",
        "correct_weight": 0.5,
        "wrong_weight": -0.3,
        "kanji_only": "",
        "kanji_type": "",
        "furigana": "ageru",
        "vocab": 3,
        "tags": "N5"
      },
      {
        "_id": "word_to_meaning_あげる_N5",
        "type": "question",
        "question": "Select the meaning for the word: あげる",
        "options": [
          "female, woman",
          "to return, to go back",
          "to give",
          "job hunting; job searching​"
        ],
        "correct_option": "to give",
        "correct_weight": 0.5,
        "wrong_weight": -0.3,
        "kanji_only": "",
        "kanji_type": "",
        "furigana": "ageru",
        "vocab": 3,
        "tags": "N5"
      },
      {
        "_id": "赤/赤い",
        "examples": [
          {
            "sentence": "このリンゴは赤いです。",
            "furigana": "このリンゴはあかいです。",
            "translation": "This apple is red."
          },
          {
            "sentence": "赤い花が咲いています。",
            "furigana": "あかいはながさいています。",
            "translation": "Red flowers are blooming."
          },
          {
            "sentence": "赤いボールを投げます。",
            "furigana": "あかいボボルをなげます。",
            "translation": "I throw a red ball."
          }
        ],
        "furigana": "aka/akai",
        "word": "赤/赤い",
        "type": "example"
      },
      {
        "_id": "meaning_to_word_赤/赤い_N5",
        "type": "question",
        "question": "Select the word with the following meaning: red",
        "options": [
          "光熱費",
          "赤/赤い",
          "次回",
          "机"
        ],
        "correct_option": "赤/赤い",
        "correct_weight": 0.5,
        "wrong_weight": -0.3,
        "kanji_only": "赤赤",
        "kanji_type": "赤:N4, 赤:N4",
        "furigana": "aka/akai",
        "vocab": 4,
        "tags": "N5"
      },
      {
        "_id": "word_to_meaning_赤/赤い_N5",
        "type": "question",
        "question": "Select the meaning for the word: 赤/赤い",
        "options": [
          "red",
          "to be concerned with, to have to do with",
          "disagreeable, detestable",
          "person’s origin"
        ],
        "correct_option": "red",
        "correct_weight": 0.5,
        "wrong_weight": -0.3,
        "kanji_only": "赤赤",
        "kanji_type": "赤:N4, 赤:N4",
        "furigana": "aka/akai",
        "vocab": 4,
        "tags": "N5"
      }
    ]
  }
}